(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-04T22:28:50.319043",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
また悪い夢を見た。
Another bad dream.
陰惨な現場が日常の探偵という職業には、悪夢は付き物と言ってもいいでしょう。
Perhaps nightmares are the penalty a detective pays for being in a gruesome business.
だが、気にしている場合ではない。
So be it. She's not about to stop.
彼女のもとに、また新たな事件が舞い込んでできているからだ。
Not when there are new cases to be solved.
(Unhappy?) 悩める人の子よ
(Unhappy?) Oh, troubled child of man,
(Unlucky?) 人成らざる者も
(Unlucky?) and those who aren't human either,
(Be happy!) 弛まず目指せよ
(Be happy!) strive without faltering.
(Undead) 生きているんだし
(Undead) After all, you are alive.
目を逸らした過去も
The past you averted your eyes from,
退屈な未来も
and the boring future too,
カウンセリング やれやれ
are still counseling you... Good grief.
古今東西 ピースピース
East and west, past and present, peace, peace!
(Unhappy?)
(Unlucky?)
(Be happy!)
(Undead)
ねえねえ ねえねえ 何だか どうして
Hey, hey, somehow, why is it
戦っているような そんな気がするの
that I feel like I'm fighting a battle?
触れられない 触れたくもない
Untouchable, don't even want to touch:
過去の自分 自分 自分 自分 と
with the past me, me, me, me...
もうとっくに死んでる 透明な亡霊と対決
Showdown with a transparent ghost long since dead.
幼気で痛い記憶の奥
In the depths of childish, painful memories,
残念? もう居ないのに
Sad? Even though it's no longer there...
あれ? そっちが良い? アイロニーね
Huh? You prefer that side? How ironic.
透かされているのは現在の自分?
Is the one being seen through the present me?
ナンセンス 消えないレッテル
Nonsense, a label that won't go away.
Yes! 要は コンプレックス
Yes! In short, a complex.
取り憑かれているみたい
It's like being possessed.
巻き付いたまま まだ 離れない
Coiled around, still not letting go.
在りし日の自分
The self from days gone by...
Undead 死んじゃいない
Undead, not dead yet!
お前とお前の連鎖
A chain of you and yourself.
生きていることとは 変わり続けることだ
To be alive means to keep changing!
不幸に甘んじて
Don't settle for unhappiness
満足するなよ
and be content with it!
幸せになろうとしないなんて 卑怯だ
Not even trying to be happy is cowardly.
この世 この世は 奇怪 奇怪 ファンタジー
This world, this world is a bizarre fantasy.
次は鬼が出るか 蛇が出るか
What will come out next, a demon or a snake?
出会って 遭って やっと 始まる 物語
Meeting, encountering, a story finally begins!
さあ人か 化物か
Now, is it human or monster?
閑話休題 ピースピース
Back to business, peace, peace!
Past & future
Can't change the past
Run for the future
カ・カ・カットイン
C-C-Cut in!
何だか どうして 未来になんぞ
Somehow, why is it that in the future
何の希望もない 期待出来ないような気がして
I feel like there's no hope, nothing to expect?
もう随分生きてる 既視感とテンプレで食傷
Lived long enough, sick of déjà vu and cliches.
素敵な出来事の気配もない
Not even a sign of anything wonderful happening.
残念 積んだ経験の因果
Too bad, the karma of accumulated experience:
形骸化された神話と退屈な進化
hollowed-out myths and boring evolution.
要は 刺激が欲しいんだ
In short, I just want excitement!
飽きちゃった 慣れちゃった
Got sick of it, got used to it.
なんて 整っていくガイダンス
Such is the guidance taking shape,
増えるコンプライアンス
increasing compliance,
蓋されていくみたい
like being put under a lid.
吸い尽くして
Sucking it all dry...
あれも これも どれも 同じ味がする
That one, this one, whichever, all taste the same.
あー 同じ アンチが ぐるぐる
Ah, the same haters going 'round and 'round...
UNDEAD!
信じない脳内 脳内の連鎖
Unbelieving mind, a chain reaction in my head,
一卵性も過去も未来も今にあるんだ
Identical twins, the past, the future—it's all right here in the present.
生きていくだけ愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill your life with foolish honesty!
目指せハッピーエンド
Aim for a happy ending!
UNDEAD!
信じない脳内 生きているんだ
Unbelieving mind, I am alive!
幸せを諦めてしまうな 独り言
Don't give up on happiness—just a monologue.
ただ苦しみになれてさえ耐えているだけじゃ
If you just endure and grow accustomed to the pain,
死んでいるも同然 屍
You're no better than dead—a corpse.
UNDEAD!
悩める人の世
In this troubled world of men,
人ならざるものも 開幕目指すよ
Even those non-humans aim for the opening curtain!
生きているんだろう 命減ったって
Aren't you alive? Even if life diminishes,
幸せになるのも どうせ未定の未来なら
Becoming happy is an undecided future anyway.
お前だ ここで起死回生
It's up to you—turn the tables right here!
一切合切 死なない証 ピースピース
Everything, proof of being undead—peace peace!
Past and future, can't change the past
Past and future, run for the future
人となあるとトコトン やっとめぐった
Living as a person, we finally met.
生きて行こうか 負けも知ら...
Shall we live on? Without knowing defeat...
ダメダメダメ 脳味噌の中からやめろ馬鹿と叫ぶモラリティ
No, no, no—from inside my brain, morality screams, "Stop it, you idiot!"
ダーリンメミーダーリン 半端なくラブ ときめき破滅的フィロソフィー
Darling, baby darling—an outrageous kind of love, a throbbing, destructive philosophy.
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い
A deadly cute, upward glance,
何かしらの法に触れるくらい
That probably breaks some kind of law.
散らまく乱心 気づけば投身
Spreading madness everywhere, before I know it, I jump right in.
この世に生まれた君が悪い
It's your fault for being born into this world.
やたらとしんどい 恋の患い バラバラになる頭とこの身体
This lovesickness is ridiculously painful, my head and body falling apart.
頸動脈から愛してるが噴き出て アイリスアウト
"I love you" bursts out from my carotid artery—IRIS OUT.
一体全体どうしようこの思いはどうしよう
What on earth am I supposed to do with these feelings?
肋骨の奥をどうしよう 砂糖の芯が溶けてゲロになりそう
What do I do with what's deep inside my ribs? The sugary core melts, turning into vomit.
瞳孔バチ開いて溺れ死にそう
My pupils blown wide open, feels like I'm drowning to death.
今この世で君だけが大正解
Right now in this world, only you are the correct answer.
ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン
Darling, darling, darling, darling...
ひっくり返っても逆立ちしても勝ち目なんかない
Even if everything turned upside down, I'd have no chance of winning.
君だけがルール外 奴等もれなく黒しかない角取り兄弟
Only you are outside the rules, while everyone else is nothing but black tiles on a board.
君が笑顔で放ったアバダケダブラで額に傷痕残ったまま申し訳ねえな
The Avada Kedavra you cast with a smile leaves a scar on my forehead, sorry about that.
矢を挿して 貫いて ここ急所点
Shoot the arrow, pierce right through—here's my weak spot.
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い
A deadly cute, upward glance,
何かしらの法に触れるくらい
That probably breaks some kind of law.
散らまく乱心 気づけば投身
Spreading madness everywhere, before I know it, I jump right in.
この世に生まれた君が悪い
It's your fault for being born into this world.
偽物でもいい 何でもいい
Fake or not, it doesn't matter, anything is fine.
今君と名付いてる全てが欲しい
Right now I want everything that bears your name.
頸動脈から愛してるが噴き出て
"I love you" bursts out from my carotid artery—
アイリスアウト
IRIS OUT.
一体全体どうしようこの思いはどうしよう
What on earth am I supposed to do with these feelings?
肋骨の奥をどうしよう 砂糖の芯が溶けてゲロになりそう
What do I do with what's deep inside my ribs? The sugary core melts, turning into vomit.
瞳孔バチ開いて溺れ死にそう
My pupils blown wide open, feels like I'm drowning to death.
今この世で君だけが大正解
Right now in this world, only you are the correct answer.
ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン
Darling, darling, darling, darling...
アイリスアウト
IRIS OUT.
ある殺人事件を調べてほしいという匿名の依頼。
An anonymous request asking to investigate a murder case.
手紙に被害者の情報はほとんどなく、ましてや犯人の情報は皆無であった。
The letter contained almost no information on the victim, and none on the culprit.
あまりに不可解な謎の手紙。イタズラの可能性もある。けど…
An overly cryptic, mysterious letter. It could be a prank, but...
おや？
Oh?
おはよう、アーニャ！依頼された絵が完成しましたよ～。
Good morning, Anya! I finished your commissioned drawing~
一伊那爾栖（にのまえ いなにす）。この町一番の肖像画家だ。
Ninomae Ina'nis. The top portrait painter in this town.
あの…私の顔に何かついてます？
Um... is there something on my face?
事件の手がかりがない以上、解決の糸口を見つけるには彼女の才能を頼る必要があった。
With no clues to the case, I needed her talent to find a breakthrough.
アーニャ？
Anya?
とはいえこういった事件では、誰もが容疑者になりうる。
However, in a case like this, anyone could be a suspect.
そう、この純粋で可憐なイナでさえ―
Yes, even this pure and lovely Ina—
わぁぁーっ！
WAH!
うわっ！
Whoa!
ごめんなさい。じーっと見られてたからつい…。どうかしましたか？
Sorry! You were staring so intently... Is something wrong?
いや別に…それっぽい雰囲気を出そうとしてただけ。
No, not really... I was just trying to create a detective vibe.
それより、頼んでた絵はできた？
More importantly, is the drawing I asked for finished?
できました〜！
Yes, it is~!
描きましたけど、それ誰なんですか？
I drew it, but who is that anyway?
Who's this a picture of anyway?
The victim from a case I'm working.
Anyway, you're charging the standard fee, right?
Sorry, but can you put it on my tab?
But you put the last one on your tab too...
Maybe we could do a trade then? I'll solve one case for you for free.
Oooorrr... I'll trade you for a song~
Or... I'll trade you for a song.
Huh?
Come on! You've been so serious lately.
You gotta get loose sometimes.
You gotta unwind sometimes.
So one song with me, and you get to keep the picture. That's the deal~
If that's what you want, then alright!
大きな白いキャンバスに 虚構のコラージュを貼るよ
On a big white canvas, I'll paste a collage of fiction.
どこからんでも綺麗に映る 誇張された天使がいたよ
An exaggerated angel that looks beautiful from anywhere was there.
まだ人と言うには新しくなくても見えた 起きるため立ち寄った美術展のセザンヌに
Even if not new enough to be called a person, I saw it in Cézanne at the art exhibition I stopped by to wake up.
何も分かんないままただ知らずに見ても勝てた 赤 ずっと塗り込んだばっか 嫉妬すぐだった
Even looking without understanding, I won. Just layered on red, jealousy followed quickly.
気取り筆の画家だけどそこがいいな
A painter with a pretentious brush, but I like that about them.
くだらない異彩だなそのまま
Such a meaningless, unique color, just as it is.
切って貼った皮 抱いてみえた嘘
Skin cut and pasted, a lie seen while embracing.
笑うように浮いたあまら
Surplus floating as if laughing.
ぎゅっと裂いてから 泣いてないから
Tearing it apart tightly, because I'm not crying.
投げつける壁に描いたパブロ・ピカソ
Pablo Picasso drawn on the wall it's thrown at.
なぜか私のことだなあって眺めてたよ
For some reason, I stared at it thinking it was about me.
これが欲しいなって感じたらシャネルの絵を希望する
If I feel like I want this, I request a Chanel painting.
なんてね 同人画取られてじっと見てたよ
Just kidding—having my fan art taken, I stared intently.
欺瞞 嘘 重ねれば本物の意味あるのかな
Stacking deception and lies, does it hold any genuine meaning?
真実はいらないまま重なり落ちて床で死んでた
Without needing the truth, layering and falling, dying on the floor.
犯人(ホシ)かすっと乗り込んだよパズルっとよかった
The culprit slipped in quietly, glad it fit like a puzzle.
言い妖しい線だな今のまま
What an eerily suspicious line, just as it is now.
切って貼った皮 抱いて知った鼻
Skin cut and pasted, a nose known through holding.
笑うように見えた身体
A body that looked as if it were laughing.
ぎゅっと抱いたから 抱いてないから
Because I held it tightly, because I didn't hold it.
投げつける壁に描いたパブロ・ピカソ
Pablo Picasso drawn on the wall it's thrown at.
私 嘘のピカソ
I am a fake Picasso.
Finally.
This is a creepy place to make someone wait.
I told you I'd come to the nearby KFP after investigating the crime scene.
Not a chance!
It's bad enough I have to talk to you. I don't want others to be around to see it.
I'm surprised you're willing to cooperate in the first place.
Yeah, well, ever since the murder, weird things have been happening.
I figure if you can help solve it, then it's worth the trouble of meeting with you.
Just barely.
What weirdness?
Some of my employees have been complaining about seeing a shadowy figure.
They say it started with bad dreams, but now some are seeing it even when they're—
Anya!
I'm... fine, don't worry about me.
Look at this.
Hmph. Course. You're just always being overly dramatic... huh?
Weird. I figured the cops would have already collected all the evidence.
Did any of your employees who live nearby know the victim?
Nope.
Alright. Let me know if you hear anything else.
Wait!
That's it? You're not even gonna compensate me for my time?
I thought you were doing this to help your employees.
I'm still a businesswoman.
Well, I don't have any cash on me, but I can pay you in song.
Seriously?
You think I'd want to sing? With you?
Ina accepted payment in song.
But then, singing with her is fun.
With you...
With me, what?
You don't think I'm good enough for you?!
Let's go, punk! You and me, right now!
全部全部あんたのせいだ
It's all your fault, all of it
ヘドが出るくらいにうざったいわ
You're so annoying I want to throw up
何かに縋って へつらって
Clinging to something, flattering everyone
期待した私がバカだった
I was a fool for expecting anything from you
ご機嫌伺いの八方美人
A people-pleaser kissing up to everyone
綺麗事言わなきゃ死ぬ病気
Suffering from a disease where you'll die without superficial platitudes
浅いキャパシティ 毎度おおきに
Shallow capacity, thanks as always
詰まるところ人生ずっと地味
Bottom line is your life is completely plain
泣き出しそう？ 泣き出しそう？
About to cry? About to cry?
無神経なのがいっそ腹立たしい
Your insensitivity is all the more infuriating
腹立たしい そろそろ飽きたぜお行儀さんに
So infuriating, I'm sick of playing nice
来い！ 負の反動は私に
Come on! Bring the negative backlash onto me
イコール 繋がれた証
That equals proof that we're connected
切り離せない関係 晒してしまいたいわ
An inseparable relationship, I want to expose it all
これは言わば ヘイトスピーチ
This is, so to speak, hate speech
匿名性の正義を 声明に乗せてんだ
Riding an anonymous sense of justice into a public statement
鳴り止まないサイレン 狂い咲く度にキレた
Sirens that won't stop ringing, snapping every time it blooms madly
悪心行進 絶望注意報ね
Malicious march, a despair warning
ダイダイ嫌いなその顔
That face I hate so, so much
私 ダイダイダイダイダイ嫌い
I hate, hate, hate, hate, hate it
お前！ 能無し 情けない もう バイバイバイバイバイしたい！
You useless, pathetic thing! I just want to say bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
脳内！ もう予測不能ゆえに 会会会会会話はない！
Inside my brain! Unpredictable, so no talk-talk-talk-talk-talks!
どう代？ 私のこと あなた ダイダイダイダイダイ嫌いになった？
How about it? Do you hate, hate, hate, hate, hate me now?
ああ 100害あって1利なし
Ah, a hundred harms and not a single benefit
何の成果もなし たられば塗れ デモ・ニコチンだし
No results achieved, covered in "what-ifs", but still like nicotine
I miss you 天地開闢
I miss you, creation of heaven and earth
結末は Vomit Vomit Thank you 反面教師
The ending is vomit, vomit, thank you negative role model
後味一生消えていかないわ
The aftertaste will never disappear for the rest of my life
よしよし良い子ね 笑顔振りまき バラバラ良い子ね
There, there, good kid, scattering smiles, broken good kid
だけど だけど その本性は 善悪の区別もつかないの？
But, but your true nature, can't you even distinguish good from evil?
限定方式で通ります 環境に巻かれて
Passing through limited methods, swept up in the environment
障害 大大 抱えきれないわって 当然の報いに喰らっちゃった
Screaming "I can't handle these huge obstacles", hit by the natural karma
人は儚いなんです 実際のところ 偽物返事です
People are fragile, in truth, giving fake responses
シャットダウンしても付きまとう 己の弱さが甲斐性ない
Haunting me even after shutting down, my own weakness is hopeless
全部全部あんたのせいだ
It's all your fault, all of it
ヘドが出るくらいに止まんないわ
It won't stop to the point of making me vomit
いっそのこと切り離した方が 分からなくなるね
If we just severed ties, we wouldn't even know anymore
ダイダイ嫌いなその顔
That face I hate so, so much
私 ダイダイダイダイダイ嫌い
I hate, hate, hate, hate, hate it
お前！ 能無し 情けない もう バイバイバイバイバイしたい！
You useless, pathetic thing! I just want to say bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
脳内！ もう予測不能ゆえに 会会会会会話はない！
Inside my brain! Unpredictable, so no talk-talk-talk-talk-talks!
どう代？ 私のこと あなた ダイダイダイダイダイ嫌いになった？
How about it? Do you hate, hate, hate, hate, hate me now?
ああ 100害あって1利なし
Ah, a hundred harms and not a single benefit
何の成果もなし たられば塗れ デモ・ニコチンだし
No results achieved, covered in "what-ifs", but still like nicotine
I miss you 天地開闢
I miss you, creation of heaven and earth
結末は Vomit Vomit Thank you 反面教師
The ending is vomit, vomit, thank you negative role model
後味一生消えていかないわ
The aftertaste will never disappear for the rest of my life
へぁ、もう誰なの？
WHAT!
はーい
Come in.
アーニャ、ヤッホー！
Hey, Anya. Ya doing okay?
って、大丈夫そう？ なんか顔色悪いね
You look kind of... not great.
大丈夫...じゃないかもね
Thanks... maybe not.
ちょっと横になった方がいいんじゃない？
You just need sleep!
マリオグラブル走ってあげるから、わための数を数えるといいよ
Lie down, and I'll run in circles so you can count me~
心配かけてごめん。でも今寝たらダメなんだ
Sorry, but not now.
なぜならあともうちょっとでこの事件を解決できそうなんだから！
I'm close to cracking this case wide open!
そう？
You sure?
そうかも... そうじゃないかも...
I don't know! Yes? Maybe?
分かんないけどとりあえずヒントは揃ったんだ
I do have all the hints...
ほな難しいか...
That doesn't seem very sure...
わため先輩、ほどほどにしておきましょう
Watame-senpai, I think you're annoying her.
わためは悪くないよねぇ！
Watame did nothing wrong.
これが事件を解く鍵なんだ。探偵の直感がそう言ってる
This is an important clue! I can feel it in my gut,
でもDNA鑑定では何も分からなかった
but a DNA trace was a dead end.
じゃあ、これは何なんだ？ これは何なんだ？！
So what does it mean? What does it mean?!
その布でそんなにお困りなら...
That it's a mean cloth?
あ、じゃあわためが食べてあげる！
Oh! I could eat it.
ねぇアーニャ、それちょっと見せてくれる？
Hey Anya? Can I take a look at that?
この布について分かったことはあるけど...
If I tell you something about this cloth,
それを教えたら、ちょっと休憩しない？
will you agree to take a break?
一旦仕事の手は止めて、私達と遊ぼうよ
Maybe do something fun with us before you go back to work?
じゃあ、一緒に歌うのもどう？
We could sing together.
この街では情報は歌で買うものみたいだし
That seems to be the going rate for information around here.
お〜、楽しそう！
Oh, that sounds fun!
オッケー、その布には魔力の痕跡を感じるんだ
Alright... I can sense a magical residue on this cloth.
そんなバカな
That can't be true.
忘れたの？アイリスはネフィリム
Hey, I'm a nephilim, remember?
魔力を感じ取るなんてお手のもの
We get a bonus to detect magic!
あれ？アーニャもこの布が怪しいと思ってたんじゃないの？
Wait... you already had your suspicions about the cloth, didn't you?
そ、そうだけどさー でも殺人事件と超常現象なんて混ぜたらダメな奴でしょ？
Yeaaaaah... but supernatural stuff happening in a murder case? They're not supposed to mix.
そう？ でもそういうアニメとかドラマも...
Really? But in some shows-
まあまあ、ぶっそうな話はそのくらいにして... みんなで歌っちゃおう！
Enough murder talk. Let's sing~
この路地を抜けろ awake now
Run through this alley, awake now
僕ら 覚醒 アップデート ey
Our awakening update, ey
ギラギラ 光らせた
Shining brightly
いいな いいな そのカラット
How nice, how nice, that carat
目立っちゃうな 自然に視線を独り占め
Standing out naturally, monopolizing all eyes
この手口は盗めない
This technique can't be stolen
答えなら「好きなだけ」が極まってく 1秒前完全アップデート ya ya
If there's an answer, "Doing as I like" reaches its peak—a total update 1 second ago, ya ya
不安グッバイ 自分以外は敵じゃない お利口御無用 指を立てろ
Goodbye anxiety, no one is an enemy except myself. No need to act proper, point your fingers
ha〜 揺れろ 運命 ah〜 あたしらしい ウルトラ C
Ha~ Shake your fate, ah~ That's our Ultra C
その感情を燃料に持ち込む 延長戦へ全能
Using those emotions as fuel, heading omnipotent into overtime
嗚呼 体が
Ah, my body
この生き様で make some noise
Make some noise with this way of life
見舞う we gotta go メディカルボイス
Delivering it, we gotta go medical voice
宿した熱狂は伝播する 真っ向から着弾
The passion inside spreads, hitting directly head-on
もらうわ大歓声
I'll take the huge cheers
burn out na na uh!
what I want to touch down
燃やせ 革命 アップデート hey
Burn it up, revolution update, hey
go all out
僕が 覚醒 逆転 ey
My awakening, reversal, ey
ひとりきりじゃ just kidding
All alone? Just kidding
君とだから dreaming
Because I'm with you, dreaming
間違いだらけ勘違いもして ときめきをリテイク
Full of mistakes and misunderstandings, retaking the excitement
ey 失っても尚コンティニュー
Ey, even if lost, still continue
支払った対価の自分 あの日に... uh
The price I paid for myself, back on that day... uh
してないわけない後悔
No way I don't regret it
胸に飾れ 前向き直せ 唱えて
Adorn your chest, look forward again, chant it
諦め悪いって？ 信じてくれ
"A bad loser?" Believe in me
青く燃ゆる僕は炎
Burning blue, I am a flame
時は経てど 恋うは心
Though time passes, longing remains in the heart
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ あたしだ
Who is it, who is it, who is it? It's me
さあ お任せ
Now, leave it to me
burn out na na uh!
ha〜
ha~
この生き様で make some noise
Make some noise with this way of life
見舞う we gotta go
Delivering it, we gotta go
メディカルボイス
Medical voice
臆した逆境に下剋上 とうとう役満
Overturning the feared adversity, finally a grand slam
あげるわ大団円！
Giving you a grand finale!
burn out na na uh!
what I want to touch down
燃やせ 革命 アップデート hey
Burn it up, revolution update, hey
go all out
僕が 覚醒 逆転 ey
My awakening, reversal, ey
以上がこちらで調べた情報です。いかがですか？
So that's everything I've got so far. What do you think?
ここは大空警察。数々の難事件を解決してきた優秀な警察から今回の事件に関するさらなる情報を得るべく、探偵は警察署を訪れていた。
And so, here she visits the Oozora Police. With their stellar track of solving mysterious cases like this one easily, she hopes that they can give her some leads.
ばっからー！事件の捜査は我々プロに任せておけばいいんだよ！
I think you should leave the investigating to the professionals.
何？被害者の服に魔力の痕跡があったって？
I mean, magical residue on the victim's clothing?
そうだ！そんなバカな話があるか！
Yes! That is very silly!
こいつ、次、自分自身が凶器かもしれないとか言い出すんじゃないですか、署長！
Next, she's going to tell me that SHE's actually involved and might be the murder weapon.
それだ！
Wait, that's it!
はぁ？
Huh?
こいつ今、自分が凶器だって自白した？
Did she just confess to being the murder weapon?
よく分かんないっす
I'm not really sure.
ボクが言ったのはただの冗談で...
What I said was just a joke...
もしかしてボク、無意識のうちに真実をつかんでいたのか！？
Could it be that I subconsciously knew the truth all along?!
お前天才か！？
Are you a genius?!
おや、これはいよいよ事件解決...
Oh my, could this mean the case...
になってしまうのか？
...is finally solved?
事件解決しちゃった！
I solved the case!
違う違う。私は凶器じゃないですよ。
No, no. I'm not the murder weapon.
異議あり！さっき自白しただろ！
OBJECTION! You already confessed just now!
私が言いたいのは、この事件にはまた別の古代兵器が関わっているかもしれないということ。
What I mean is, another ancient weapon might be involved in this case.
だから布に魔力が残っていたんだ。
That's why there was magical residue on the cloth.
なんだ、そういうことか...
Oh, so that's what it was...
僕が事件を解決できたと思ったのに...
And here I thought I had solved the case...
まあ次がんばれよ。
Well, try harder next time.
でもなぁ、現場の近くで変なものを見たっていう報告も届いてるんだ。
But you know, we've received reports of people seeing weird things near the scene.
その魔力の痕跡とやらが超常的な力によるものだって言うなら... 変な幻覚が見えた人がいるのもそいつの影響ってこと？
If that magical residue is caused by supernatural powers, does that mean the weird hallucinations people saw were also its doing?
それはまだ分かりませんが、謎は必ず解いてみせましょう。
We don't know that yet, but I will definitely solve this mystery.
じゃあうちの捜査資料を持って行っていいよ。
Then you can take our investigation files with you.
民間人にあげちゃダメっすよ！
You can't give them to a civilian!
でもこいつさぁ、なんか天才の匂いしね？
But doesn't she kind of seem like a genius?
さっきはボクのこと天才って言ったじゃないですかぁ...
You just called me a genius a moment ago...
どんな情報でも助かりますよ。
Any information would be helpful.
ただし！資料が欲しいなら、タダというわけにはいかんな！
However! If you want the files, it won't come for free!
これ、また歌う流れですか？
Is this turning into another singing segment?
それは知らない 何も知らない
I don't know that, I know nothing.
何も見てない 誰も見てない
I haven't seen anything, nobody has seen anything.
空を見ての 見えない夜の
Looking up at the sky, on a night where you can't see,
欠けた月に 密かに
secretly under the crescent moon.
これはなんだ それは何か
What is this? What is that?
ここは試し それで宜しい
This is a trial, is that fine?
走る逃げる 逃がす探す
Running, escaping, letting escape, searching,
好きな欠けた 場所へ
to a favorite broken place.
アララ...
Ah-ra-ra...
もうさ 咎められなく
That's right, without being blamed,
そうさ 咎められなく
yeah, without being blamed,
衝動 収まらず
an uncontained impulse,
なぜか なぜか 知らん
for some reason, I don't know why.
最悪だ 厚重の靴を履いて 脱いで踊れ
It's the worst! Put on heavy shoes, take them off and dance!
最低感 なんでなんでっつって なんか何かと重なって
The worst feeling! Asking why, why, overlapping with something or other.
最悪だ どうもこうもしねえよ 勝手にしやがれ
It's the worst! Nothing can be done, do whatever you want!
最低感 いやもう本当 最悪だーだーだーだーだー
The worst feeling! No really, it's the absolute worst!
誰のせい？ 誰のせい？ 憑き纏う 見える意識の裏側に
Whose fault? Whose fault? Hauntingly clinging to the reverse side of conscious mind,
大きく開いた黒い穴 分かる 分かる 分かる
a big open black hole. I understand, I understand, I understand.
許す 許せん 許す 許せん
Forgive, unforgivable, forgive, unforgivable.
可愛い えへへ 怖い
Cute, ehehe, scary.
りんご
Apple,
ゴリラ
gorilla,
落語
rakugo,
こちら
this way,
ラクダ
camel,
ダブル
double,
ラマダン
Ramadan!
私達 絶対に見てません 聞いてません 知ったこっちゃありません
We definitely didn't see anything, didn't hear anything, it's none of our business!
光を疾走 影に一突き 許されざる思考を 当てはまらない情を 綴って生きていこうじゃありませんか
Sprinting through the light, a thrust in the shadows, shall we live on spelling out unpardonable thoughts and unfitting emotions?
鼓動 狂おしく
Wild heartbeat,
狂躁 意味もなく
meaningless frenzy,
エゴ 自己満足
ego and self-satisfaction.
だから...
So...
最高だ 脳が硬化してんだ ぶっ壊して叫べ
It's the best! The brain is hardening, smash it and scream!
最高感 なんでなんでっつって まこまこはねちゃって
The best feeling! Asking why, why, Mako-Mako is bouncing!
最高だ 好奇心で結構 勝手に生きたれ
It's the best! Curiosity is fine, live as you please!
最高感 いやもう本当 最高だーだーだーだーだー
The best feeling! No really, it's the absolute best!
昔 昔の思い出つき 無意義 無意義の人ばかり
Old, old memories attached, full of meaningless, meaningless people.
無邪気 無敵の生まれつき それが それが
Innocent and invincible by nature, that's it, that's it.
責任集合体 あんたもわたしも関係ない
Collective body of responsibility, you and I have nothing to do with it!
責任集合体 楽しくやってりゃもう満開
Collective body of responsibility, as long as we're having fun, we're in full bloom!
勝手にやってりゃ問題なし それは知らない 何も知らない 何も言わない 何も...
If we do as we like, there's no problem! I don't know that, I know nothing, I say nothing, nothing...
ない
No
ちょっと
Wait a sec
違い
No, that's wrong
夢の話
A story about dreams...
そういうカットで
Cut it like that.
それじゃ
Well then...
超常的な力が殺人事件に関わっている？
A supernatural occurrence, happening in a murder case?
いやいやそんな、ねぇ？
That's just unbelievable, right?
にわかには信じがたいが、今の手がかりから推理するとそういうことになる。
She had a hard time believing it, but all the hints said otherwise.
まだパズルのピースがピタリとはまらないこの不思議で奇妙な事件。
Still, there were pieces of this puzzle that refused to fit in this strange case.
探偵は信頼できる情報源に頼ることにした。
So the detective turned to a reliable source for help.
あっ、来てくれたー
Ah, I'm glad you came!
...なんで君達まで？
...And why are you guys also here?
We heard Zeta was coming over, and decided to bug ya!
Yes, yes. I see.
Aww, come on!
Anyway, Zeta, did you find anything?
Of course! I'm not an elite secret agent for nothing!
Between the portrait from Ina and the files from the Oozora Police, I've been able to positively ID the murder victim.
But... what I found is weird.
How so?
Well, when I investigated their history, I found that they actually lived centuries ago.
So how they were also somehow murdered just days ago... it doesn't make any sense.
Did you perhaps confuse your information? Or...
Actually, things are finally starting to make sense.
Oh?
A victim caught between two times.
One who died in two different ways.
Not many exist who can cause time and dimensions to warp in a way to make that possible...
...but you're one of them.
Well done, detective.
Took you long enough. I was this close to telling ya the whole thing.
You helped enough with this "anonymous" letter about the murder.
O-oh, you figured out that was me?
I recognized your writing style.
W-wait, I don't get it. What does Moona have to do with the victim?
She took a murder victim from another space and time, and moved them into our dimension.
The one you IDed was this universe's version of the same person.
Uh... okay. But then why?
That is an important question, but there's one I want answered even more.
Are you... responsible for my dreams?
No.
After I learned about your dreams, I used my powers to search for the source of them.
I found a spirit reaching out from time and dimensions.
All I've done is try to help them by making the bridge a little easier...
With my help! I mean, it was my idea...
True.
Though doing it this way has caused some of what you've been experiencing to leak to other people.
We're going to have to apologize to the KFP workers...
But why is the spirit reaching out to me of all people?
It wouldn't be right for me to answer those questions. It's not my story to tell.
Open yourself up to the spirits, and they'll do the rest.
I got a way to make yourself more open to spirits!
Is it through song?
Huh? How'd you know?
Lucky guess...
思い返してた 思い出の中で泣いてた
I was looking back, crying in my memories
負担しかない夢と孤独を抱えて笑ってた
Carrying dreams and solitude that were only burdens, I laughed
この畳み掛く質問 堪えないゴミに言い返してしまいそうな
About to talk back to these relentless questions and unbearable nonsense
焦りと不安がにじんで 涙に飲まれてしまう
Impatience and anxiety bleed through, swallowed up by tears
誰一人欠けることはない ちぐはぐな
Not a single person is missing from our mismatched...
僕らの思いが音になって繋ぐ
...feelings that turn into sound and connect us
こだまして忘れないようかき鳴らして
Strumming so it echoes and won't be forgotten
あの日僕らは間違っていなかったんだと知る
Knowing that we weren't wrong on that day
伸ばして仕舞い込んだ一線の光探して
Reaching out, searching for that ray of light tucked away
君の声を聞かせて ここにいるって叫んでくれよ
Let me hear your voice, shout out that you're here
その手を離さないで
Don't let go of that hand
世界に僕だけが取り残されてしまう
I'll end up left behind all alone in this world
…んだよな
...right?
暗闇の中で立ち止まり 手放してしまう
Standing still in the darkness, letting go.
心が通じ合えないのなら 心殺してしまうなら
If our hearts cannot understand each other, if we must kill our feelings...
一人でいた方が楽に生きられたのかな
Would it have been easier to live alone?
憧れ 理想に強く惹かれる感情が
If feelings strongly drawn to longings and ideals...
僕らを 引き寄せてしまうのなら 応えて
...pull us together, then answer me.
誤魔化していーく まだ終わっちゃいないんだ 僕ら延長戦なんだろう
Deceiving, keeping it up... It's not over yet. We're in overtime, aren't we?
この音が途切れるまで
Until this sound fades away...
子供の頃に描いたヒーロー
The hero I envisioned as a child...
君の出番が待ってる
...your turn is waiting.
誤魔化していーく 忘れないよう鍵鳴らした意味を
Deceiving, so as not to forget the meaning of ringing the key.
あの日僕らは間違いじゃなかったと知る
We come to know that we weren't wrong that day.
閉ざしてしまい込んだ一線の向こう側探して
Searching for the other side of the line we locked away,
君の声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice.
ここにいるって叫んでくれよ
Shout out that you're right here.
その手を解かないで
Don't untie those hands.
魂に心を開け？ 簡単に言ってくれる。
Opening up to the spirit? That was a tall order.
探偵になる前の彼女の人生において、他者に心を開くのは危険な行為だった。
In her life before being a detective, opening up to someone was dangerous.
今でもその本能は変わらない。
That instinct still lingers.
結局何もしんてんはなかった。
This was getting her nowhere.
謎はまだ残っているが、彼女はここのところ無理が続いていた。
She still had questions she needed answered, but maybe she had wound herself up too much.
少し休まなければ。
She needed a break.
Hello everyone! I'm Hatsune Miku, a virtual idol!
Well, that's what everyone seems to think at least... Right?
Oya oya oya oya!
Miku-chan! Anya-chan!
Anya-chan! 一緒に歌おう！
Anya-chan! Let's sing together!
I wake up to a call, put my frilly outfit on now
It’s time I open up my eyes and start the day
I combat till the dawn until every villain’s gone
A clumsy trip and now I’ve fallen to my butt
With my magical phone and a silly little ringtone
I’ll shout a magic word and set the world in place
Whatever it may cost, there’s no reason to stop
For a world that I cherish and love
Monsters might be a scary foe to fight
But I’ll take the stand if I can stop your tears and wipe them dry
I’ll make you feel M@GICAL!
If my pain's a type of cure for peace, I don’t mind. I can play as a nurse healing you everyday
So what if I might shed a tear, get some bruises?
A wipe is all I need to clean the cherry blush away, ha!
Fighting through the night, but I’m wide awake
It can all be so hard for me to get through the day
Your smile is enough to heal all my aches
Wrapped in a cute band-aid
I can take the pain, fight all day
Fill up the syringe with love
Heal up the world and go again
Super powerful Miku-chan!
Miku Miku Miku go!
And now, it's time for the moment you've been waiting for!
1! 2! 3! Ready?!
Miku Miku beam!
Keep going!
On my own, without anyone to know
How my job’s not all rainbows
But then I think about your smile... (Your words are so lyric☆l)
I’m a magically bright invincible girl!
If you need me to heal, go on and call out my name
When you find yourself going down a spiral
I’ll bonk away what puts you down, a pink hammer melee! Yah!
Fighting through the night, but I’m wide awake
All alone it’s so hard for me to get through the rain
Your smile is enough to make my day
So I stand tall and brave, ‘cause I’m not afraid
Any pain I can laugh away
Chin up, with love I’ll fight on till the end
Bearing through the pain, I'll try to be brave
As long as you can stay happy, I'm okay
I'm not gonna bend, ha!
I can be a cure for peace in your heart and I'll play as a nurse healing you everyday
Your smile is enough to heal all my aches
So in a cute band-aid
If you're feeling pain, call my name, I'll be by your side
Till I see your smile beam bright again
Oya oya oya oya ooh! Fighter! Super powerful Miku-chan!
Oya oya oya oya ooh! Cyber! Miku Miku Miku GO!
あぁ、眠いよ〜
Ah, I'm so sleepy...
あっ
Ah!
夢...だった？
Was it... a dream?
知った
I knew...
救いのない形だった
It was a form beyond salvation,
僕の声は
my voice was.
知った
I knew...
救いのない赤い血が流れているんだ
Irredeemable red blood flows within me.
ただただ襲い来る影ばかり
Shadows that endlessly attack,
揶揄う言葉 立ち上がれない夜風
mocking words, a night wind keeping me down.
赫く光る場所へ 裸足で駆け出したら
When I ran barefoot toward the red shining place,
ただただ膝を抱えている貴方がいた
you were there, simply holding your knees.
だから
So...
ENCOUNT!
悲劇ぶった天国へ
Toward a heaven playing tragic.
不甲斐ない瞳
Pathetic eyes,
きっとあの日みつめた
that surely stared at those days,
貴方のせいで
all because of you.
はやく はやく...
Quickly, quickly...
身を委ねて
Surrender yourself.
淡い水面の向こうと
Beyond the faint surface of the water,
視線
a gaze.
知った
I knew...
救いのない熱を持った
Possessing a heat beyond salvation,
僕の炎波
my flame wave.
歌った
I sang...
憂いのない貴方の眼は醜かった
Your sorrowless eyes were hideous,
酷く
so cruelly...
呆然としているその顔に触れてみたかった
I wanted to touch that stunned face of yours.
だから
So...
ENCOUNT!
喜劇ぶった天国へ
Toward a heaven playing comedic.
奪い合う瞳
Eyes claiming each other,
屹度 あの日
surely, that day
崩れた
that collapsed,
貴方のせいだ
it was all because of you.
はやく はやく はやく...
Faster, faster, faster...
ねえ 教えて
Hey, tell me.
深海 樹海 秘密のむこうへと
Deep sea, sea of trees, to the other side of secrets.
不甲斐ない瞳
Pathetic eyes,
屹度 あの日
surely, that day
偽った
lied,
君のせいだ
it was all because of you.
はやく はやく はやく...
Faster, faster, faster...
息を止めて 泡や泡になり むこうへと
Hold your breath, turn into bubbles and foam, to the other side.
白い光をみつめていると
When I stare at the white light,
急な痛みに襲われる
a sudden pain attacks me.
僕が私を保っていられなくなること
That I can no longer maintain myself,
それをこの小さな器が証明している
this small vessel proves it.
初めに 安堵する君がみたい
First, I want to see you relieved.
次に 期待したい
Next, I want to have expectations.
この場所で戦いなど起こっていない。
There was no major battle here.
少なくこともこの世界線では...
At least not in this timeline...
だが探偵には分かっていた。彼女が見たものは決して夢ではないことを。
But the detective knows what she saw was no dream.
心の中にはまだ殺戮の匂いが漂っている。
The smell of the carnage still lingers in her mind.
かつての彼女にまとわりついていた、あの匂い。
It's a scent that was, at one time, so familiar to her.
探偵としての生活も今では順調だが、そうでなければあの匂いからは離れることができなかったでしょう。
That stench would still linger on her if the detective's life didn't take a turn for the better.
今でも...あの頃の日々がリアルな夢のようにまとわりつく。
Even now... her days felt more like the real dream.
終わるべくして終わったおとぎ話。
A fairytale. Maybe one that deserved to end.
どこまで行っても彼女は、生まれ持った本質から逃れることはできない。
Because, at the end of the day, she can never run away from her nature.
それでも今は違う。今の彼女には仲間がいる。
But she's not just that anymore. She has friends to thank for that.
それが、別の世界線の彼女とは違う点なのかもしれない。
Maybe that was what separated her from the other version.
もしかしたらあの子は、幸せに生きることのできた世界線があったのだろうかと、
And, maybe... that version of herself just wanted a ray of hope,
そんな一筋の希望を求めていたのだろうか。
to know that there was one timeline where things worked out.
そしてその幸せな世界線というのは、ここではないまた別の世界線のことかもしれない...
Or perhaps this was never about the detective...
考えが頭を巡るものの、答えが出ることはない。
so many thoughts run amak inside her head, but they're forever left unanswered.
何にせよ、探偵は自身の血塗られた過去を忘れることはないでしょう。
Whatever the case, the detective won't forget her bloody past, but she isn't going to revert to it either.
しかしまた後戻りするつもりもない。彼女はこれからも仲間とともに進む。
She will continue to move forward with her friends,
望んだ結末を迎えられなかった別の自分たちのためにも。
and for all the variants who didn't get their desired ending.
探偵アーニャ・メルフィッサは、
The detective, Anya Melfissa,
明日に向かって生き続ける。
will keep on living for her own tomorrow.
Anya Melfissa Birthday Live 2024!
How did everyone like it?!
Oh, my goodness!
やっと今年も参りました、アーニャの誕生日です！
It's finally here again this year, it's Anya's birthday!
いかがでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
This time, I tried to incorporate a little bit of story into my 3D birthday celebration,
and I think it turned out pretty nice, you know?
You get story part, and also live part,
and I think it turned out pretty well!
And also, how was my new original song? Oh, my goodness!
How was my new original song? It was good, wasn't it?
I hope you all liked it.
新曲もね、あの、歌わせていただきました。いかがでしたでしょうか？
I was able to perform my new song too. How did you like it?
Ah! Oh my god!
I celebrated my birthday with a lot of friends too this year.
Yeah, a lot of the girls came to celebrate my birthday,
and also Detective Anya managed to solve that mission.
Wow, she's got it! Detective Anya.
Did you guys like Detective Anya as well?
Detective Anya was pretty cool, but not as cool as me!
Oh my god, and also special guests!
There were special guests!
Oh my god, I can't believe I got to sing with Hatsune Miku! Hatsune Miku-chan!
Oh my god, she was really cute!
And also for the narration for my story part, Ueda Reina-san narrated it!
Oh my god! 上田麗奈さんがやってくれました！
Oh my god! Reina Ueda-san did the narration!
ありがとうございます！ミクちゃんとも歌ったし、いや盛りだくさんでしたねー、今年。
Thank you so much! I sang with Miku-chan too, it was packed full of stuff this year!
Oh my god, lots of wild things happening on this year's birthday live! How did you guys like it?
How did you guys like it? Oh my gosh!
Yeah, I had a lot of fun! But...
I would like to make an announcement this year. It's the usual!
ここで告知があります！
We have an announcement here!
I have an announcement to make! Let me make an announcement!
はい！こちら！
Yes! Here it is!
Oh my god, what is that? Who is that? Is that me? Yes, it is! We're releasing some new merchandise this year!
What do we have? Let's take a look at them, shall we?
そして、えーっと、1つずつ見ていきましょう！まずは、こちらです！
And, um, let's take a look at them one by one! First is this one!
It's a canvas art! "Study Time with Anya!" Canvas art!
Oh my god, this illustration is so cute! It's illustrated by Lunar-sensei!
Lunar先生に、イラストを描いていただきました！可愛い！
Lunar-sensei drew this illustration for me! Cute!
The theme is, you know, literary girl. Oh my god, so smart, so intelligent!
文学少女というテーマになっております！
It has the theme of a literary girl!
次はこちら！
Next is this!
"Study Time with Anya!" The notebook!
I think this is my first notebook! I've never had a notebook as merchandise before! Oh my goodness!
Please use this lots for all your notes, for anything!
色々メモしてね！オリジナルノートでございます！
Take lots of notes! It's an original notebook!
と、次はこちら！
And next is this!
It's a pen case! How cute is that! ペンポーチです！
It's a pen case! How cute is that! It's a pen pouch!
ペンポーチも初かな？ ノートも初らしい、ペンポーチもなんと、初です！
Is a pen pouch a first too? The notebook is a first, and the pen pouch is also a first!
ぜひ一緒にね、あのノートと使ってください！
Please use it together with the notebook!
Use this along with the note, I think they would go really well together, okay?
次はこちら！
Next is this!
今年もボイスが出ます！そして今年もえー、アーニャが台本を書かせていただいております！
There's a voice pack again this year! And Anya wrote the script again this year!
I wrote the script as usual, as usual for every year! I wrote the script for this situational voice, so please get it! Please get it!
Oh yeah, the voice will be in Japanese, but there will be scripts in Indonesian, English, and Japanese!
ちなみにボイス自体は日本語になりますけど...
By the way, the voice audio itself is in Japanese, but...
えっと、台本もついて...ついてきます！インドネシア語と英語と日本語の台本があります！
um, scripts are... scripts are included! Scripts in Indonesian, English, and Japanese are included!
ぜひ聴いてください！
Please listen to it!
そしてフルセット購入特典はこちら！
And here is the full set purchase bonus!
Oh my god! Limited Edition Birthday Set has... what is that? A hand-signed autograph?! Oh my god, it's the first for me! Anya's first-ever hand-signed autograph for Limited Edition! Please get them!
なんと、今年はサイン入りです！
It comes with a signature this year!
今年はサイン入りです！なんと、なんと、なんと！初、初ですね！アーニャが自らサインをして... 初なので、ぜひ皆さんこの機会でゲットしてください！
It comes with a signature this year! Wow, wow, wow! It's the first time Anya is personally signing them... Since it's a first, please take this chance to get it!
Yeah, please get the Limited Edition! And for the Standard Edition, it includes a foil-stamped replica autograph, so don't worry if you miss out on the Limited Edition! Yeah!
ということでグッズ紹介は以上です！That's all for the merch!
So that's all for the merchandise intro! That's all for the merch!
Introduction!
And another announcement is that my original song, the one that you guys heard...
...it's called ENCA or ENCOUNT, by the way.
It will be releasing digitally in like a few hours!
It will be releasing digitally at 12:00 AM your time zone...
It will be releasing digitally at 12:00 AM in your time zone...
...at 13 March!
...on March 13th!
Yay, yippee!
So in like... in like a few hours, yeah!
So in like a few hours, yeah!
Yay! なんとね
Yay! Also,
デジタルリリース、新曲のデジタルリリースもあります。
the digital release, my new song's digital release is coming as well,
13日の0時です。
at midnight on the 13th!
よろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
そしてこの後、メンバーシップで配信もするのでぜひ見てください！
And after this, I'll be streaming on membership, so please make sure to watch!
There will be a special encore for members-only after this!
So members, Melhomies, let's go!
So members, Melfies, let's go!
There will be a membership-only stream after this!
So please come and watch! It'll be... It'll be 3D, by the way!
So you guys might want to check it out!
Yippee!
Okay, are you guys ready? Are you guys ready?
Well, this Live is ending, but we still have membership after this.
So I will see you guys there!
For members, I'll see you guys there,
and for non-members, thank you so much for coming and for watching my 3D birthday live!
I hope you guys enjoyed it!
Thank you, thank you!
And I wonder if you guys also posted a lot using the hashtag. I sure hope you guys did!
Yay! Thank you so much!
And おつくリス！ Bye-bye! おつくリス、everyone!
And Otsukuris! Bye-bye! Otsukuris, everyone!